serence.com 2006-06-23

# serence | company | privacy policy

| | |   
---|---|---  
**Privacy Policy**  
 **Terms of Use**  
 **Trademarks & IP**  
| Privacy Policy

Serence is committed to the privacy of its web site visitors and product end users. Please note that we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**Personal Information**  
In order to respond to your questions, fulfill your requests, or allow you to complete a survey, it may be necessary to ask for personal information such as your name, address or e-mail address. We may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you via mail or e-mail to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. If you place an order for a product or request a service, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfill your order and/or request. We will not provide this information to any third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, or fulfill your request.

PRIVACY NOTICE  
As of January 1, 2004, the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act requires every organization to obtain the consent of individuals before collecting, using or disclosing personal information. As a Klip provider, forum participant or other Serence contact you have entrusted us with a variety of personal information. We use this information to administer your account and communicate with you. We safeguard this information with appropriate security measures to ensure this information remains bound to the aforementioned purposes only. Your trust in Serence is of utmost importance to us as we continue to value your relationship with us. 

If at any time you have questions regarding our privacy policy or the accuracy of information in your account, please don't hesitate to email us at [info@serence.com](mailto:info@serence.com).

**Security**  
Serence has taken appropriate measures to prevent unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your personal information.

**"Cookies"**  
From time to time, we may place information on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is commonly known as "cookies". By showing how and when our visitors use this Site, this information can help us to improve our service experience on a continual basis. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many Web sites use them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so.
